Guide to the Alfred E. Kahn papers, 1942-1994
Kahn, Alfred E. papers, 1942-1994
- Series XIII. Kahn's Subject Files Alpha
  - Airlines, Financial, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Airlines - Foreign Ownership, 1992 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Airlines - Frequent Flyer Programs, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Airlines Government Assistance, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Airlines - Hub Dominance, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Airline Labor, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Airline Mergers, 2006 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Airlines - Misleading Advertising, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Airlines: New Entrants, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Airlines - Override Commission (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Airlines - Predation, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Airlines - Pricing, 2006 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Airlines - Regulation Mexico, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Airlines - Safety, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Airlines - Statistics, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Airlines - Travel Agents, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Airports, 2000 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Airports - Congestion, 2008 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Airports Council International Keynote Address 8th Regional Conference 10/25/99, 1999 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Airports -Single Till, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Airport Slots, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Airports (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Airports - Tompkins County, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Airport Rentals, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Air Traffic Controllers, 2001 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Alberta Northeast Gas, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Alleghany Power, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Alternate Operator Services, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Alberta Gas, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Alzheimer's, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - American Antitrust Institute, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - American Heritage Dictionary, 1996 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Ameritech, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Archives - Cornell (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Argentina, 1997 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Arizona Public Service, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Arkansas Power & Light, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Ashley Creek, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Asia, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Aspen Ski Coporation, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - ATA/Buckeye Pipe Line, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - AT&T: Regulation NYC 12/2/82, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Cornell University - Macroeconomics, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Joel, Dirlam, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - International Aviation, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Memorandum File, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Talks, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Telephone Company Pricing, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Western Electric, 1982-83 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - AT&T, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - AT&T, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - AT&T - Cream Skimming, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - AT&T - Docket 18920, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - AT&T Separations, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - AT&T Prices, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - AT&T Private Line Rates, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - ATCO, 2000 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - AT&T, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - AT&T "A Grand Competitive Strat.", 1969 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - AT&T: Access Cost Studies, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - AT&T Alarm Antitrust, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - AT&T Asset Transfers, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - AT&T: Baumol, Eckstein, Kahn, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - AT&T Consent Decree, 2006 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - AT&T Depreciation, 1997 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - AT&T Diverstiture, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - AT&T Exchange Access 5/84, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - AT&T Exchange Access Charge, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - ATTIX AT&T Interexchange, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - AT&T 83-1147 New Reg., 1942 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - AT&T - New Reg., 1984 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - AT&T - New Reg.: Docket 87-313, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - AT&T/NYT, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - AT&T Separations, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - ATT/TCI, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Antitrust, 1985-86 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Australia, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Australia - Aviation Policy, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Auto Industry, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Autobiography, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Aviation Policy Clinton, 1993 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Avoided Costs, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - BA/USAir, 1993 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - BAA Counterclaim, 1993 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Balance of Payments, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Bank of America, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Dave Barry, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Barsky, Arthur (Joe) & Susan, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Baumol, William J. (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Baumol-Eckstrom-Kahn. "Competition and Monopoly in Telecommunications Services", 1970 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Baumol-Bailey-Willig-Panzar, 1995 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Beer, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Bell Atlantic, 1993 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Bell Atlantic Collocation, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Bell South, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - Bernstein, Caryl, 2006 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - Best, Arthur, 2005 (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - Best, Rachel, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - Bidwell, Miles, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - Blue Ribbon Panel Final Report 1/23/01, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - BOCs Current, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - Boston Edison, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - Boone, Peter S., 2006 (Box 98, Folder 30)
  - Borders, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 31)
  - Peter Bradford, 2006 (Box 98, Folder 32)
  - Brands - TELRIC, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 33)
  - Brazil, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 34)
  - Breyer, Justice Stephen G., 2006 (Box 98, Folder 35)
  - British Airport Authority, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 36)
  - Briefing Note: Effect of Change in Logan Fees, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 37)
  - British Airways, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - British Gas, 1996 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - British Mercury, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - British Telecomm., 1991 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Broadband, 2009 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Brooklyn Union Gas, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - H. G. Brown, 1999 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - BT-MCI, 1996 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Bipartisan Budget Appeal, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Bubbles, 2000s (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Budget Cuts, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Burlington Northern & CNW (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Bus and Coach Council, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Bus Deregulation, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Bypass, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - C-7, 2001 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - C & P Telephone(Chesapeaka & Potomac) (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Cable Regulation, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Cable TV, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - TV: Fines, Interest & Syndication, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Cable TV - Telco Ownership, 1995 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - CAB Sunset 9/21/84, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Canadian Communication Policy, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Canadian Competition Bureau - Standard Electric Supply Service, 1999 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Obligation to Serve Capacity Reservation Charges, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Carron, Andrew: NERA Economic Consulting, 2007 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - Jimmy Carter, 2007 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Casten, 2004 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Cellular Radio, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Centel - Illinois/Florida, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Central Hudson Gas & Electric, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Central Maine Memo (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Cereal, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - CMP Hydro Quebec, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - CMP: Pricing Transmission Services, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Champlain Pipeline, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - China, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Clean Air Act, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Bill Clinton, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Coal Rates(1), 1992 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Coal Rates(2), 1983 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Coal Rates - The Netting Issue, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Coal - Section 2C, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Coal - Slurry Pipeline, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Coal Rates - Utility Fuels, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Cogeneration, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Collective Consumption Decisions, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Columbia Gas, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Combination Companies, 1996 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Comcast/Disney, 2007 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Commercial Messaging, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Common Cause - Ithaca, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Commonwealth Edison, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Communications, General, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - Communications Depreciation, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - Communication Deregulation, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - Communications: Mobile Telephones, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - Communications: Spectrum Allocation, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - Computer Chips, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - CRS-Delta-Salre, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - COMSAT, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Con Edison Acquisition Premium, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Con Ed - Meeting, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Conkling, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut Cable Television, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Conrail, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Conspiracy, 1990s (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Construction Work in Progress, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Consumer Price Index, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Contestability, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - COPE, Hal, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Copeland, Morris, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Hugh Corbet, 1985 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Cornell 1969, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Cornell - Business, 2000 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Class of '64 Talk 1/30/99, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Club, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Cornell University - Development, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Dept. of Economics, 1999 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - CU - ScholarsFirst, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Cost Benefit Analysis, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Cost of Capital, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - COX Cable, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Cramton, Peter, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Credit Cards, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Cross-Subsidization, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - CSX/ACBL, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - CUDAHY, Judge Richard D., 2009 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - DACA Reports, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - DACA Universal Service, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Democracy Party, Statement of Long-Term Economic Policies, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - DEMPSEY, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Denver Air (Stapleton), 1989 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Denver Water Authority, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Depreciation, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Deregulation I, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Deregulation II, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Destrcutive Compet., 1991 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - DHL, 2001 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Diefenbach, Jane(Boone), 2006 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Disneyland, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Disposable Income, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - DOJ Ameritech (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - DOJ, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Dow Jones, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Drugs, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Dukakis, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Dumping, 1993 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - East West Airlines, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Eastern Airlines - Lorenzo, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - Eastern Europe, 1997 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1992 (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - ECPR, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - Econometrics, 2003 (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - Economic Advisory Group 1969 - A Grand Competitive Strategy, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - Economic Growth + E+D Investment, 2009 (Box 99, Folder 26)
  - Economic Indicators - GPO, 2009 (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - Economics - General, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 28)
  - Economists Against the Arms Race, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 29)
  - Economics of Regulation, 1999 (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - Edison Electric Institute, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Education, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - EEI Rail Revenue, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Election 2000, 2000 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Electrics - Antitrust, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Electric Deregulation Workshop, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Electric Power - California, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - EPRI Rate Design, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Electric: Retail Wheeling, 1994 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Electric Utilities, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Electric Utilities - Avoided Cost, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Electric Utilities - Bidding (Competitive Bidding, Auctions), 1990 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Electric Utilities - Conservation(1), 1991 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Electric Utilities - Conservation(2), 1991 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Electric Utilities - Conservation(3), 1991 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Electric Uitilities - Deregulation, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Electric Utilities - Diversification, 1997 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Electric Utilities - Financing, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Electric Utilities & Envision - Mental Regulation, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Electric Utilities: Holding Companies, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Electric Utilities: Incentive Regulation, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Electric Utilities: IPP's, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Electric Utilities: Least Cost Planning, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Electric Utilities: Marginal Costs, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Electric Utilities: Market to Book Ratios, 1995 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Electric Utilities: New vs. Old Customers, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Electric Utilities: Obligation to Serve, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Electric Utilities: Performance, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Electric Utilities: Price Squeeze, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Electric Utilities: Promotional Rates, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Electric Utilities: Public Power, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Electric Utilities: PURPN, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Electric Utilities: Rates, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Electric Utilities: Rate of Return, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Electric Utilities: Restructuring, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Electric Utilities: Structure, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Electric Utilities: Takeovers and Consolidation, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Electric Utilities: Telecommunications Ventures, 1999 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Electric Utilities: Vertical Integration, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Electricity - Demand, 1989 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Electricity and the Environment, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Eelctricity Generation, 1979 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Electricity - Pooling, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - Electricity Prices, 2001 (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - Electric Magnetic Fields, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Emerson, Peter, 2007 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - Empagram, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Employment Cost Index, 1988 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Energy, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Energy Association of NY State, 2001 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Energy Conservation, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Energy Conservation Coalition, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Energy Efficient, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Energy - Greenhouse Gases, 2009 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Energy Modeling Forum, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Elec. Utilities Transmission, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Energy Research Group, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - ERG Mettings, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Enron, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Environment, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - EPA, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - ERG-FERC Paul Joskow Comments/AEK Replies, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Eskin, Evelyn, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - ESCOs (Energy Service Co.), 2000 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Essential Air Services, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Essential Facilities, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Ethanol, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - ETSI, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Express Mail, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Express Mail Cross-Exam, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Externalities (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Europe, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Falk, Jonathan, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Fascism, Nazis, etc., 2004 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Faulhaber, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - FCC- Collocation, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Federal Communications Commsion, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - FCC Computer 3, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - FCC Fairness Doctrine, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - FCC- Financial Interest And Syndication Rules, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - FCC Price Caps, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - FCC - Media Ownership, 2008 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - FCC Order, 1996-98 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Federal Bar Association, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - FERC - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - The Free State Foundation, 2009 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Frieden, Professor Rob Penn State University, 2008 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Foer, Albert(Bert), 2006 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - FOX, Professor Eleanor, New York University, 2007 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Future Writing, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Gas Pipeline, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - GEDDES, Professor Rick, Cornell University, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Georgiadis, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - Gifford, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - Ginsparg, Paul, 2007 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - Globalization, 2008 (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - Global Warming, 2008 (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - Gore, Senator Albert, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 30)
  - Grieve, Willie Chair, Alberta Utilities Commission, 2007 (Box 100, Folder 31)
  - Gaskin, Darius, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 32)
  - GTE Depreciation, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Guam Shipping, 2002 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Gulf States, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Hahn, Robert (Bob), 2007 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Harvard Business Review, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Hazlett, Thomas (Tom) W., 2004 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Head Start, 1989 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Health Care, 2004 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Herman, Professor Edward S., 1996 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Congressman Hinchey, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Hirsh, Richard F., 1997 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Housing, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Howard, Cabanne, 2001 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Hudson Institute, 1996 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Hydro-power (Small), 1985 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - IMF, 1998 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Immigration, 2002 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - ICC Interstate Commerce Comm., 1982 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - ICC: Railroad Revenue Adequacy, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Income Distribution (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - Indexation, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - India, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - Indiana Telephone, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Industrial Policy (1), 1985 (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - Industrial Policy (2), 1991 (Box 101, Folder 25)
  - Inflation, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 26)
  - Inflation Accounting, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Inflation Watch, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Insurance, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Intercompany Coordinator, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Intermediate Communication, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Internet Broadcasting, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1952 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Interstate Natural Gas, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - IRAQ, 2004 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Italy, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Ithaca Journal, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Ithaca Nerighborhood Housing Services, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Jackson, Chuck, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Jaskow, Jules, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Japan, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Jersey Central, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Johnson and Jonnson, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Joel's Book, 1986 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Kahan / Spirit Airlines, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Kahn Brothers, 2005 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Kapuni Gas, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Kendall Corp. (Retirement Home), 1992 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Kendal Correspondence, 2008 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - KLM, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Kolbe, A. Lawrence Tye, William B, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Labor, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Laker, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Lange, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - LCI, 1998 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - Levine (Michael) Correspondence, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - Liberalism Paper, 1995 (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Liberalism/Progressivism, 2006 (Box 91, Folder 32)
  - Liberman, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 33)
  - Lilco v. Cuomo (Box 91, Folder 34)
  - LILCO - Rico Suit, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Line Sharing, 1999 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Linkline, 2001 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - LMS (Local Measured Service), 1983 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Loescher, Samuel M., 1986 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Long Beach, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Lorenzo, Frank, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Lovins, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - LRIC (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - MacArthur Foundation, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - MACK, Martin NY Deputy Attorney General, 2006 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Macroeconomics, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Marginal Cost Pricing, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Martime, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Markovits, Richard S., 1989 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Mauro, Dr. Nicholas, 2007 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - May, Randolph J. (Randy) The Free States Foundation, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Mayo, 1998 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - McBride, Mike, 1999 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - McCraw, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - MCI, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Mc Carty Farms, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Mercury, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Medical, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Madicare, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Memorable Communications, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Mergers, 2003 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Mexico, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Mexico Telecom, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Microsoft, 2007 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - Microsoft & Trinko, 2006 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Midtec, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Miller, Edith, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Milk, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Minimum Wage, 1998 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - MIT Communications Policy, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Mobile (Alabama) Airport, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Monetarism, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Monetary Policy, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Morrissette, Hughes + Family, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Morse, Chandler, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Mountain Bell, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Mudge, Dick, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Multipart Pricing, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Municipal Distribution Agencies, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Nafta, 2007 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Nat'l Council on Public Works Improvement, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - National Institution of Economics And Law, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - NTIA Nat'l Telecommunications & Info. Admin., 1986 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Natural Gas, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Natural Gas - Distribution, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Natural Gas - Inventory Holding Charge (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Natural Gas Pipelines (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - NBR Material, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - N. Gas Pipelines Opinion 436 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Natural Monopoly, 2005 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - NERA - Antitrust Cases, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - NERA - Business, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - NERA - ERG File, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - NERA - Gas (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - NERA Personnel Vitas, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - NERA Seminars, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - NERA Staff, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - NERA Topics (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - NERA files, 1969-1972 (Box 136)
  - Net Demand, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Net Taper Extension, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Neumann, Richard D., 2009 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - New England Electric, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - New England Telephone, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - New England Telephone, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - New England Telephone - Massachusettes, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey Central, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - New Framework Group, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey Beer, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - New York Port Authority, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - New York State, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - NY State Bar Association Policy Board on Regulatory Reform, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - NYS Council on Econ. & Fiscal Priorities, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - NY State Development, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Nightly Business Report, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - NYS Economic Policy Research Council, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - NY State Economy, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 20)